It has begun.
Nighttime and Idol Dialogue Series
This is Night Orna.
And I'm Aika Kiunori from C-ON.
Please give my regards to you.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, I'm Aika Kiinuri from C-ON. So, that's why I'm here.
If I told you that I'm here as a guest, it would sound like I'm staying at night,
It's not like that,
It's almost nice to meet you.
Yes, it is. Today is the first time,
It's nice to meet you.
We might have met each other at some festivals,
But it's the first time to talk to each other.
It's our first time talking to each other,
What should I call you?
I usually call you Aikaman,
Aikaman?
Aikaman, the man who stands for justice.
So, do you introduce yourself?
I don't,
I don't say it, but I sometimes use it.
I see.
It has become a catchphrase for me,
You are also aikaman to your fans.
Yes, that's right.
Then today I would like to go by "aikaman.
I'm usually called Rumpan,
Because the staff said "Lumpang" earlier,
I thought he was calling me Lumpang.
So you abbreviate it to Lumpangpan.
Why? That's it.
I asked him to put it on,
It's "runnun-pan-pan".
That's why it's RUN-NUN-PAN-PAN, isn't it? So it became something like that,
So for a while I was called Lun Nun Pang Pang,
Then one day, he asked me, "Isn't the Lun Nun Pang Pang a little long? One day, he said, "Isn't it a little long?
It is indeed long.
Shouldn't it be Rungpan? I just thought it would be better to call it Lungnumpangpan,
It was like they just abbreviated it to RUNUNUNPANPAN.
But I like Rumpan.
I'm happy.
I'd like to go with Aikaman and Rumpan.
Please do.
So the two of us will be at the event on September 6,
We are going to perform at Tokyo Enecound Vol. 3,
Today, before the event, we are going to play a game,
We would like to deepen our friendship through a game before the event.
Let's play a game! It's a game!
Yes!
I'm so happy.
So, what's the first game?
It's a gesture game.
I would like to explain the rules.
The person who makes a gesture draws a card from the deck of cards,
Only you look at it.
The player gestures the subject written on the card.
The person who answers looks at the gesture,
The person who answers the question looks at the gesture and answers what the question is.
The goal is to get at least six correct answers in one minute.Try to get at least 6 correct answers in one minute.
Oh no. Will it go?
Can you do it? I hope it's not too hard. Is it?
As I said before, it was pretty difficult.
But I'm going.
At the meeting earlier, we were told to aim for 10,
So I'm going to do my best to get 10.
So, who will make the first gesture?
Then, let's play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
One of you makes a gesture.
Gesture.
First one goes "goo", then "rock, paper, scissors".
I made a funny voice.
Then, Aikaman will be the one who answers and I will be the one who gestures.
One-minute gesture game
Let's start the one-minute gesture game.
Trumpet, trumpet
Yes! Yes!
Selfie stick, selfie, camera, make-up, make-up, girl, pass pass pass
Fun, club, dance, what, what, what?
What's wrong with you?
What is this? What's this?
Dancing, dancing, wow! Surprise!
Pass, pass, pass, pass.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Eat, square, make, fry
oh, wait, that's really hard.
break, cucumber, uh, what to do, what to do, what to do, uh, chocolate, chocolate, chocolate, chocolate
Oh, I got it, I got it, I got it!
flamingo, uh, what's that, what's that, octopus, octopus, octopus
Ramen noodles, ramen noodles, ramen noodles? No?
uh, tantanmen, uh, what's, what's, what's, what's, what's, what's 3 minutes, cup ramen!
Yes!
That's it!
Why, what's wrong?
Here we go.
Okay, here we go.
The first one,
This is fun.
This is it.
Wow, I want to go.
Trumpets.
Trumpet.
Next, maybe a mirror.
Mirror?
It's difficult. It's going to be on this side, isn't it?
I thought I would fix my makeup when I put the mirror in.
How do I do it with a mirror?
I don't know.
What is this?
I had no idea.
Next was the trampoline.
Ah!
A trampoline!
I don't get it!
This is where they started to realize how bad I was at trampoline.
I was terrible at it.
It was even more difficult because I was sitting down.
But that was just an excuse.And that's an excuse.
Next is chocolate.
Wouldn't it be great if you could figure it out?
I thought he was a genius.
Next was cup ramen.
I guess "cup ramen" is almost the right answer.
And then octopus.
What? That makes four.
I felt like I've had about six guesses before.
I feel like I've had about eight guesses.
I didn't say that at all.
So I got four.
Now I understand how it feels.
Let's get started!
Mountain Climbing
Boxing
Foot cutter
People cutting their legs off
Angry man
Soccer
What is this?
Dancing
That's right.
Let's see...
Study, homework, tests
Cram school
Teacher.
What's this? This... this... this...
this, this, this
Tango butterfly
No, pass, pass, pass, pass.
Pass-pass-pass.
OK OK OK
cat
fox
Yay.
Uh-oh.
Bing bong dash.
What?
Here you go, takeout.
Yes, just the sound.
Interesting.
What the...
What's this?
Pass.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
What's this?
Cute cat.
It's cute.
What is it? Is that an otter-bunny?
That's it.
Ha-ha-ha.
No, no, no, but I think I did pretty well.
Hmm.
1. soccer
How did you understand it?
I understand.
I'm on the edge of my seat.
I can't use my legs.
Why are you doing this?I thought why do this?
I thought, "Why this?
Yes, it was soccer.
Next was dance.
It didn't take long.
Next was crayon.
Crayons are a little bit of a bad choice.
Oh, yeah.
Crayons are bad.
I did it when I was a little baby.
Oh, that's what you meant.
I thought it was a compliment.
Nice try.
Next is the fox.
Fox. Okay.
Next is the courier.
The courier.
I lost a member.
That was close.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
Ice cream at the end.
I should have done more.
Like this.
I didn't do it.
Is that all?
Yes, so, yes, I did each one,
I think I'll look at one of these and pick the one I think I can do best and try it.
I have to win this one for sure.
If I don't win?
If I don't get it right, I'll look like an idiot.
I see.
I have experienced this before.
Okay, then,
I've had it opened before,
Then, you did it.
I have confidence in it.
Yes, I'm sure.
I'm in. Please!
Wait, what?
What? What? What? What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What? What?
Jellyfish?
Oh, no.
Skyworms!
What? What? What?
The ocean! Ocean!
Wave!
Surf! Surf!
What is that? What is that?
Beach?
The ocean?
Wave?
Wait a minute. Isn't that a little rough?
What? What's that?
The ocean! Pool! Pool! Pool!
Swimming pool!
What's that?
Shampoo?Shampoo?
What? What? What? What?
Wait a minute. You know what?
Wait a minute.
A cold! Cold! Cold! Cold! There's a cold!
It's hard! Difficult? !
A cold?
A cold.
But you're right, it's a cold.
You're right.
If that's what they think, it could be a cold.
Wow.
It was a cold.
Yeah, you're right, it was a good one.
You're right, I'm just ignoring it. I'm a wicked person.
I'm just ignoring the fact that I have a cold.
I thought my cold looked like a cold.
I was just ignoring it
Yes, so I had a cold.
Please, please, please.
I'll go.
What? Wait. Why?
Scaredy-cat.
Aah! A ghost!
Thank goodness.
It's a ghost.
A ghostly feeling.
I see.
That's because it was cute.
I thought it was a scared cat like a cat.
What's that?
I'm glad. If I hadn't recognized it, I would have been in trouble.
That's for sure.
So...,
We played a gesture game.
Thank you very much.
It was fun. I want to do it again.
It was good.
Don't you usually don't play games like this?
I don't usually play card games.
And I'll probably never play with people I've never met before.
You don't play card games very often, do you?
How to get to know each other for the first time.
It's a gesture game.
It's not a gesture game.
The gesture game changed the way we get along.
It was good.
Next time we will try a different game.
Please look forward to it, everyone.
What a meeting so far,
Nitrna and
This was a memorial love song for Shinyon.
Bye bye.